dunkinathome.com 2016-06-07

# Privacy Policy | Dunkin' Donuts Coffee

This Privacy Policy addresses the practices of The J.M. Smucker Company relating to the collection and use of information resulting from your use of our website. If you have any questions or comments regarding our Privacy Policy please contact us. Our contact information is: 

The J.M. Smucker Company  
1 Strawberry Lane  
Orrville, Ohio 44667  
Telephone: 1-800-374-5308 

### COLLECTION AND USE OF INFORMATION

We may collect some or all of the following information from you when you visit our website: 

1) personally-identifiable information that you voluntarily provide to us, such as your name, address, email address, birthdate, and telephone number;   
2) information volunteered by you, such as survey information and/or information in connection with contest registrations; and/or   
3) aggregate and non-personal information identifying the web pages that you access or visit. 

The type of information we collect from you will depend on the web pages you access at our site. For example, you can visit our website and learn about our products without providing personally-identifiable information. However, you may be required to provide us with personally-identifiable information when ordering products from our site, registering on the site, entering our contests or promotions, completing our surveys and questionnaires, using the “Tell a Friend” or “Share This” feature on our website, newsletters or other web-based communication or using our recipe boxes on our site. Some of these uses are described in more detail below. 

_Orders_ – If you purchase a product from our online store, we will request certain personally-identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you. 

_Registration_ – You may choose to register on our site. The information requested during the registration process includes personally-identifiable information such as your name, address, email address, birth date, and telephone number. We may also occasionally send you information on products and special promotions. You can sign up for these emails from us on our registration page. If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. 

_Contests_ – We may provide you the opportunity to participate in contests on our site. If you choose to participate, we will request certain personally-identifiable information from you such as your name, address, email address, birth date, and telephone number. The requested information will also include information contained in your contest entry. 

_Surveys_ \- We may provide you the opportunity to participate in surveys on our site. If you choose to participate, we may request certain personally-identifiable information from you. The requested information will also include survey responses. 

_Tell A Friend_ – This site may, from time-to-time, include a “Tell a Friend” feature that makes it easy for you to forward information from our site to friends or family. If you choose to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. We do not store **** this information except for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. 

_Recipe Box; Recipe Rating_ – You may elect to create and maintain your own personal recipe box on our site. You may also choose to review and rate a recipe where this feature is offered. In order to create a recipe box or review and rate a recipe, you will be asked to provide your name, address, email address, and birth date. 

_Grocery List_ – You may elect to create and maintain your own grocery list on our site. In order to create a grocery list, you will be asked to provide your name, address, email address, and birth date. 

_Email Recipe_ \- This site may, from time-to-time, include an “Email Recipe” feature that makes it easy for you to send a recipe from our site to friends or family. If you choose to email a recipe to a friend, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will send your friend a one-time email containing the recipe. We do not store **** this information except for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email. 

_Social-Networking Sites_ – Certain features such as “Share This” or other social media elements available on our sites may involve features hosted by third party sites. For example, some social-networking services allow you to share content from our website through your social-networking profile. If you choose to make use of third-party social-networking services (such as Facebook or Twitter), we may receive personal information about you that you have made available through those services. You should ensure that you are comfortable with the information your third-party social-networking services may make available to our website by visiting those services’ privacy policies and by modifying your privacy settings directly on those services. Any information we receive through third-party social-networking services may be used as described in this policy. 

_Publicly Available_ Information - When you participate in the different elements of our website, including through rating and reviewing a recipe, message boards, providing tips, posting to Facebook or Twitter, or other interactive functions, you may submit information and content, such as a recipe, rating, picture, information about yourself, etc. to the site. Please keep in mind that what you post or upload to the site is available to the public, so please exercise caution when deciding whether to disclose anything personal about yourself. We cannot control the actions of third parties who may view the website and use publicly-available information for their own purposes 

_Information Collected By Automated Means -_ We may use cookies, web beacons/pixel tags, log files, and other technologies to collect certain information about visitors to our website, use of our online features, and interactions with our emails and online advertisements. For example, through these means, we may collect your browser type and operating system, viewed web pages, links that are clicked, IP address, sites visited before coming to our website, emails we send that you open, forward, or click through to our website. Collecting this information, and linking it with your personally-identifiable information, helps us to best tailor our website and enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a particular site, and to help identify site features, recipes, advertisements, and offers that may be of particular interest to you. 

We also may use third party advertisements placed by ad networks to support our site. Some of these advertisers and ad networks may use technology such as cookies and web beacons/pixel tags when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers and ad networks information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and whether you have Flash installed. Some of these advertisers and ad networks also may use anonymous data, such as demographic data, received from third parties to assist in the delivery of advertisements to you. These advertisers and ad networks use the information described above to provide you relevant advertisements based on your online behavior, search activities on our site and on other third party sites, demographic information and/or relevant to your general location, so that the advertising you see on our site more closely reflects your interests and needs. For example, if you search for or browse a, recipe or product on our site, you may see an advertisement from a third party with information about, or an offer similar to, that for which you were searching or browsing on our site, or an offer related to a third party whose site you have visited in the past. 

You can set your Internet browser settings to stop accepting new cookies, to receive notice when you receive a new cookie, to disable existing cookies, and to omit images (which will disable pixel tags). Note that the opt-out will apply only to the browser that you are using when you elect to opt out of advertising cookies. You can learn more about and opt out from receiving third party advertiser cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative’s opt-out page [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) [http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/]. Please note, without cookies or pixel tags, you may not be able to take full advantage of all of our website features. 

_Information Collected From Other Sources_ \- We may obtain information about you from other sources, including commercially available sources, such as data aggregators, public databases and other third parties. This information may include name, demographic information, interests, and publicly-observed data, such as from social media and shopping behavior. For example, if you are on another website, and you opt in to receive information from us, that website will forward to us your email address and other information about you so we may contact you as requested. We may combine this information with the information we collect from you to help us tailor our communications to you and to improve our services and products. 

### SHARING OF INFORMATION

_Personally-Identifiable Information_ – We may share information among our various businesses and brands within The J.M. Smucker Company and its subsidiaries. We may provide your personal information to third parties who provide services on our behalf. For example, we use an outside shipping company to fulfill orders, and a credit card processing company to bill for goods. We use other third parties to provide promotions, contests, newsletters and hosting for our site. These service providers may use the information solely in conjunction with the specific services they provide for us. These service providers are not authorized to use, share, retain or store your personally-identifiable information for any other purpose. We may conduct joint promotions with other companies, and may share with these promotional partners (and their service providers) personally-identifiable information necessary to conduct the promotion. We may also use and disclose personally-identifiable information where we think it is necessary to investigate or prevent actual or expected fraud, or criminal activity or injury or damage to us or others, including when requested or required by law enforcement or government officials. We will not share personally-identifiable information with unaffiliated third parties. For California residents, please see Opting Out, below. 

_Aggregate Information (non-personally-identifiable)_ \- We may share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers who perform services on our behalf. This information does not identify individual users. We do this for online data analysis and research purposes to help provide our users with relevant tool and features. We do not link aggregate user data with personally-identifiable information. 

_For California Residents_ \- We may share your personally-identifiable information with affiliated third parties, some of which do not share the name of The J.M. Smucker Company, for their own direct marketing purposes. Because this category of affiliates is considered to be “unaffiliated parties” under California Law, you may opt out of us sharing with them. To opt out, please send a letter with your name, postal address, e-mail, with the heading “California Privacy Rights” to: 

Consumer Communications Center  
1 Strawberry Lane  
Orrville, Ohio 44667 

### OPTING OUT

_Your Choices_ — As discussed above, we provide you with the option to receive marketing and promotional materials. If you no longer wish to receive our newsletters and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or by [clicking here](http://www.dunkinathome.com/unsubscribe/). If you are registered with our website, you can change the information you have provided to us by visiting your profile page on the website and changing your preferences. Be sure to click “Update Profile” for the changes to become effective. 

_For California Residents_

— We may share your personally-identifiable information with affiliated third parties, some of which do not share the name of The J.M. Smucker Company, for their own direct marketing purposes. Because this category of affiliates is considered to be “unaffiliated parties” under California Law, you may opt out of us sharing with them. To opt out, please send a letter with your name, postal address, e-mail, with the heading “California Privacy Rights” to: 

Consumer Communications Center   
1 Strawberry Lane   
Orrville, Ohio 44667 

### DISCLOSURES REQUIRED BY LAW

We reserve the right to disclose your personally-identifiable information as needed if we are required to do so by law, regulation, subpoena, or court order, or if necessary to protect our rights. 

### LINKS TO OTHER SITES

Our website may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by us. Please be aware that we, The J.M. Smucker Company, are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site. This includes reading the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally-identifiable information as the privacy policy may differ from ours. 

### HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION

The security of personally-identifiable information is important to us. We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards to protect against unauthorized use, disclosure, alteration or destruction of the personally-identifiable information we collect on this website. 

You should keep in mind, however, that no data transmitted over the Internet is 100% secure and any information disclosed online can potentially be collected and used by parties other than the intended recipient. As a result, while we strive to protect your information, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to or from our web sites. 

### UNITED STATES ONLY

This website is intended for use by residents of the United States of America only. All matters relating to this site are governed by the laws of the State of Ohio in the United States of America. If you are located outside of the United States of America and you contact us, please be advised that any information you provide to us will be transferred to the United States of America and that by submitting information, you explicitly authorize its transfer. 

### PERSONALLY-IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

In the event we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your personally-identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred to the acquiring entity. In addition, if any bankruptcy or reorganization proceeding is brought by or against us, such information may be considered an asset of ours and may be sold or transferred to third parties. 

### CONSENT TO PRIVACY POLICY

You consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy by using our website. If you do not agree with any term of this privacy policy, please refrain from using our site or submitting any personally-identifiable information. ****

### A SPECIAL NOTE TO PARENTS

We respect the privacy of all of our online users, especially children. We do not intend to collect personally-identifiable information from children under 13\. Our policy is intended to adhere to the Children's Advertising Review Unit (CARU) privacy guidelines and the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA). We encourage parents to monitor, supervise and join their children in online activities. 

### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

We reserve the right to change or replace this Privacy Policy at any time. Please check back from time to time to ensure that you are aware of any changes or updates to the notice. We will indicate the Policy’s effective date on the first page of the Policy.
